Would you be good at managing a top-level sports team?
你擅长管理一支顶级运动队吗？
Do you have the tactics and know-how to be the next Jurgen Klopp?
你是否具备成为下一个尤尔根·克洛普所需的战术和专业技能？
Well, you can find out by playing fantasy sports!
那么，来玩梦幻体育游戏就能找到答案！
While football fans across the globe observe victories, losses and draws of real matches this season, over nine million people will play Premier Fantasy Football, according to the Premier League.
根据英超联赛的说法，本赛季全球各地的球迷们关注着真实比赛的胜负与平局，同时将有超过900万人参与英超梦幻足球游戏。
And it’s not just football, but also baseball, basketball and cricket to name just a few fantasy sports you can join.
而且梦幻体育的种类不止足球，棒球、篮球、板球等也都在可选之列。
In a fantasy league, you get an imaginary budget which you can spend on your squad, selecting any players that compete in the actual sport of your chosen league.
在梦幻体育联赛中，你会获得一笔虚拟预算，用来组建自己的球队阵容，你可以从所选联赛的真实参赛球员中任意挑选。
Of course, better players cost more!
当然，实力更强的球员身价也更高！
As the real games play out, so does your fictional team.
随着现实中的比赛推进，你这支虚拟球队的战绩也会同步更新。
Doesn’t sound up your street?
这听起来适合你吗？
You may well have been pressured into competing in a league against your friends or colleagues against your better judgment, but, according to research, playing fantasy sports can actually benefit you.
你或许曾拗不过他人，不得已和朋友或同事组队参赛，但研究表明，玩梦幻体育游戏其实对你大有裨益。
Some people find they enjoy the camaraderie that comes with it even if they’re not a fan of the sport itself.
有些人发现，即便自己并非这项运动的爱好者，也能享受游戏带来的团队情谊。
In fact, a US Quantum Workplace survey found that co-workers who play in a fantasy league together, bond better.
美国昆腾（量子）职场咨询公司的一项调查显示，一同参与梦幻体育联赛的同事，彼此之间的关系会更加融洽。
They scored more highly in teamwork and trust than those who play, but not with colleagues.
在团队协作和信任度的评分上，他们比那些和非同事组队的玩家要高得多。
Plus, friendly competition gives you something to chitchat over when enjoying a hard-earned rest!
此外，这种友好的竞争还能为你在来之不易的休息时间里，增添不少闲聊的话题！
Other pros are the brain training you get along with the entertainment.
除了娱乐之外，这类游戏还能锻炼你的脑力。
Strategy, tactical decision-making, budgeting and navigating large amounts of data are just some skills you need to do well in this kind of game.
要想在游戏中表现出色，你需要掌握策略制定、战术决策、预算规划以及海量数据分析等多项技能。
So, get your team ready and good luck!
所以，赶紧组建你的球队，祝你好运！